When did you have a fever?
Look,
you don't even know
when I had a fever.
Did you get hurt in the fight?
Now you're showing concern for me.
You should drink less.
Uncle,
why did you come back so late?
Haoyu
went to help out at my performance,
to save my show.
He didn't do anything wrong.
What show?
I actually like rock music.
I formed a band.
It's good to have a hobby.
And,
I think everyone
has a different side.
So does Li Haoyu.
He's not the bad kid
as you think.
As for the fight,
you can ask Director Qian.
He's more reliable than that parent.
I'll think about it.
You should get some rest.
You too.
Okay.
Dad.
I won an award.
I won an award, look.
You won another award?
Let me see.
Campus Story Competition,
champion.
How do you feel?
Happy.
I'm even happier than you.
When I was in school,
I never won an award.
Other students
told stories from fairy tale books,
but I made up my own stories.
Everyone said they were very interesting.
Impressive.
My son won an award.
Champion.
Haoyu is awesome.
Auntie Xie.
Thank you, Auntie.
Did you tell Dad it was a bluff
or made up?
Made up.
Really?
Then go home and tell Dad
how you made it up.
No problem.
Dad,
I've won the championship.
Do you have any reward for me?
What do you want
to eat?
I'll cook for you.
Rice noodles.
I want rice noodles made by dad.
Okay.
Champion rice noodles.
Exclusive for Haoyu.
I'm going to eat rice noodles made by dad.
Champion rice noodles.
There's a Young Drummer Competition
in the city this fall.
Let's learn to play the drums together.
Why are you always
wanting to enter various competitions lately?
I want to win awards.
I'm not like you,
with good grades,
winning trophies and certificates every day.
Did your dad let you take it?
My dad is not your dad.
He doesn't expect much from me.
And
he seems
to be busier now,
especially since we moved into the big house.
So you want to win trophies and certificates
to get more attention from your dad?
I've decided
to learn to play the drums
and win this award.
Dad.
You say these.
I know all these.
I don't need to know
the reason now.
Just give me the results.
Okay?
Dad.
I won first place
in the citywide young drummer competition.
I've only been learning for half a year.
Half a year?
How come I didn't know?
Yeah.
Show me.
First place.
Awesome.
Dad.
I want stir-fried noodles.
Sure.
Every time you win,
I'll make you stir-fried noodles.
Champion noodles,
just for you.
Okay.
Tell me.
Understood.
I'll handle it.
Wait for me.
[Haoyu,]
[there's an issue at Dad's company.]
[so I have to go there.]
[I can't make]
[stir-fried rice noodles for you.]
[How about this?]
[I'll transfer some money to you.]
[You can order]
[delivery yourself.]
[Order something tasty.]
[Okay?]
[You won a prize.]
What reward do you want?
Pick a gift for yourself,
okay?
Don't play with water
or fire at home.
I'll be back soon.
See?
Because my book report
was so good,
my teacher
appointed me
as the reading committee member.
From now on,
I'll collect all the reports
during Reading Week
and submit them to the student union.
How's that?
Impressive, huh?
Thank you.
Gu Chenyang,
you're the reading commissary of Class 1, right?
From now on,
we're competitors.
Not competitors.
We're all
good partners in the Student Union.
That's right.
You're so insightful.
President,
this is my book report.
You three
better work hard.
Don't get left behind.
I'll excuse myself
due to my busy schedule.
Is he
okay?
He's usually so cheerful.
Something's up.
Jiang Yi told me
his dad had a big fight
with him yesterday.
Seems like he said a lot
to undermine him.
Should we
find a way
to comfort him?
He seems carefree,
but when something's really bothering him,
I don't know how to
truly comfort him.
I think I have an idea.
This is all the data
I've collected and organized
about Xie Yizhou
during this period of time.
Although it's limited,
it's enough for you to know
what kind of opponent
he is.
The Institute's Middle School has always been strong.
With him on their team,
it's going to be harder for us.
Exactly.
Fu Binyan
has analyzed not only Xie Yizhou,
but also each of your
strengths and weaknesses.
He's covered everything.
Next, Gu Chenyang and I
will develop a new strategy
based on this analysis.
I hope we can
create another glory in the next game.
Yes!
Yibei will win!
There is another
important thing.
We need to formally commend
our talented and versatile
outstanding and sunny Li Haoyu.
Please.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Li Haoyu
is the shooting guard
of our team,
and the best one.
So,
the first award
we're going to present
is jointly sponsored by
our coach Su,
manager Chi Jia,
data analyst Fu Binyan,
the manager Chi Jia,
and the photographer Xu Anbo.
Yeah.
You actually remember
that I want an award.
Of course.
Li Haoyu is also
an excellent drummer
and the captain.
So,
the second award
we'll give him
is jointly sponsored
by Zhou Yang, the guitarist
Lin Qingyuan, the bassist
Gu Chenyang, the keyboardist
Fu Binyan, the violinist
and Fang Xu, the lead singer
of the OTC Drugs
and Jiang Yi, the guitarist.
jointly sponsored
by Yibei Best Drummer Award.
Okay.
I'm a bit nervous.
This award is quite significant.
I feel honored
to present it
as an intern coach.
The third award
is sponsored
by our Dean Qian.
Yibei Most Improved Award.
Applause!
Okay.
One is
a signed
Most Improved Award
from Director Qian,
and the other is Best Senior Award from Chen Song.
Are you trying to
get rid of me?
We just want you to know
in our eyes,
you've always been the best.
The best.
You're the best.
I know that.
Alright,
let's take a group photo
to remember this moment.
Okay.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Here.
Let's make a "yeah" gesture.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Haoyu.
Dad made stir-fried noodles.
Dad, you are...
Let me see.
Best Guard in Basketball Award.
Sit down first.
What a coincidence!
Do you remember when you were a child,
whenever you got an award,
I would ask you what you wanted as a reward,
and you would say you wanted my stir-fried rice noodles.
It's a coincidence today.
I made stir-fried rice noodles and you won an award.
The Best Senior.
Eat.
About the thing last night,
I talked to Director Qian on the phone.
He told me
the whole story.
It was indeed
a misunderstanding.
Eat it while it's hot.
But anyway,
he shouldn't have hit you.
Be careful in the future.
Do you think
I'm too strict with you?
Honestly,
we don't
have many chances
to talk like this.
You can
say whatever you want.
What did you ever care about?
Yeah,
I'm too busy
with business,
and sometimes I don't care about you enough.
But Haoyu,
you should
understand me.
Li Haoyu,
you can't say
I don't care about you at all.
Are you
saying that to me?
Do you think
I don't care about you?
You...
You may have cared about me.
I heard you had a nickname
at school,
Troublemaker-in-Chief.
You're like this even when I do care about you.
If I don't care about you,
what would you be like?
If you have a child in the future,
will you talk to him?
Will you educate him?
If I say a few words,
you'd say I'm too preachy.
If I'm not paternalistic,
what should I be?
If I'm not paternalistic, am I still your father?
Alright.
Dad, don't talk so much.
Eat while it's hot.
No.
Can you understand
what I'm saying?
A little bit.
Okay.
I'll be happy if you can.
I'm easy to please.
Eat.
It's too salty.
Do you think it's too salty?
I think it's fine.
Stop eating.
I'll make you another one.
It's okay.
I'll just
make you another one.
It's too salty.
Give it to me, Dad.
I just like this bowl.
Didn't you say it was too salty?
Didn't you say it wasn't salty?
Li Haoyu has made significant progress this semester.
He's no longer at the bottom of his grade.
Thanks to his teammates
for helping him with his lessons.
The basketball team is also doing well.
They just formed a team,
and they won the game
against last year's runner-up,
Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education.
I have many photos.
I'll send them to you.
By the way,
at the Arts Festival,
their stage play
won first place.
Li Haoyu was the lead,
and he also led a band.
It was a great honor for the school.
Director Qian,
I've been busy
with business these years.
I thought boys
could be raised freely.
Now I see
I haven't been
a good father.
It's not too late
to be a good father
from now on.
Why didn't Fu Binyan like my post?